A Finding Aid to the Organization of Independent Artists Records, circa 1970s-circa 2003, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition and Installation Files, circa 1970s-circa 2003; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 13 Linear feet Boxes 5-18
  - Eye On Art (1992), circa 1992-circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32-33)
  - New Images in Stone (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34-35)
  - New Images in Stone (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Persistence of Subject (Selection) (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Spare Parts (1992), circa 1992-circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4-6)
  - Real Paintings (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Refiguring the Form (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
  - Urban Alchemy (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
  - Eye on Art (1993), 1992-circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12-15)
  - Idio Cognito (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Infused with the Spirit (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - The Issue is Life (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Line-Up: At the Police Building (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Mindscapes: Abstraction and Experience (1993), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Object Lessons (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
  - OIA Salon Show (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Outdoor Sculpture (1993), circa 1992-circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25-28)
  - Outdoor Sculpture (1993), 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Repair Work (1993, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Selections from the Slide File (1993), circa 1992-circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Signs of Life (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - That Is a Hat (1993), circa 1992-circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Twisted State (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - VisionTelevision (circa 1990s), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Visual Aids (1993), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Copier Art Show (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Critics' Choices (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Critics' Choice III (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Fire Without Gold: Six Photographers of Color (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Five Women Sculptors - Cinco Escultoras (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15-20)
  - Landscapes: Seen and Remembered (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Making Evidence (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - OIA Salon Show (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23-26)
  - Out of Line (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Paper Dolls (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Raw Materials (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Selections from the Slide File (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Valparaiso (Chile) Biennial (1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Behind the Eight Ball (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - By Design (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Curve Into Cursive (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Expert Testimony: Russian Installations (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Friends, Family, Hearts and Flowers (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Internal Examination (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mindscapes, Abstraction, and Experience (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - OIA Art and Design Silent Auction (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - OIA Salon Show (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12-17)
  - Paint and Circumstance (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Physical Sense (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Questioned and Embedded (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Sculptors' Thinking Drawings (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Selections from the Slide File (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Six Views of New York: Cityscape Paintings (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ten from the Salon (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Unwanted Figures of the Imagination (1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - The Body Autonomous (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Darker Visions (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fire Without Gold (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Landscapes (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Passages (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30-31)
  - Passages (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Salon Shows (1996-1998), circa 1996-circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5-7)
  - Saving the Scene (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Selections of Small Works from the Slide File (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Thresholds Reflections Transformations (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Beyond the Surface (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Image in Abstraction (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Installing Nature (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Loosen Up and Enjoy Art Again! (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Mass Mediums (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
  - Of the Body (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Painted Black: An Exhibition of Paintings (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Reflections of Experience (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Sister Dreams (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Thin Thread (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Urban Landscape (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - When Worlds Collide (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Amazons and Avatars (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Animal Magic (1998), 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - City Light (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - The Critics' Choice: Ten from the Salon Show (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Digital Visions: The Creative Edge (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Drawing the Line (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Fighting Weight (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Layered (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Media Madness (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Medicinal Madness (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Self (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - A Show of Vessels (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Subtle Jolts (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Views of Summer (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Wall-to-Wall (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - @ Maya Art Exhibition (1999), circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  - Abstract By Nature (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Balancing Acts (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Barroquism (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Big Apple (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - City Portraits (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Conventional Still Lifes (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Food for Thought (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Four Reflections of Our Expanding Universe (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - From Union Square to Battery Park: 5 Painters (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Gotham Living (1999), circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - A Millenium of Memory (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Nesting (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Nude/ Naked (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Photographic Memories (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Places in Time (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Pregnant Sculpture (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Reconstructed Human Surfaces (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Refrigerator Magnet Show (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 25-27)
  - Seascapes (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Sense of Place (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Storytellers (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Thinking Digitally (1999), circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Touching Time (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Wild Things (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - IV - Interior Visions (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 2nd Refrigerator Magnet Show (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Bricks and Mortar (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The Cat Show (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Critics' Choice (2000), 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - Elements 2000 (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - Exotic Embellishments (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - The Fertile Mind (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Fireworks - artistBooks (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Mapping Spaces (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Mosaic (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Needs - Unmet (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Patterned Behavior (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Petrogenesis: The Origin of Rocks (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Similar by Content (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Sleeping on the Beach: Four Artists from Miami (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Undercurrent (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Y2K-aotic: Uncensored All-Media Salon Show (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20-21)
  - Automatic Drawings (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Aylene Fallah Exhibition (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - The Critics' Choice - From Small Works Salon Show (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Different Voices (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Elise Engler: Everybody Gets One (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - The Insomnia Show (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - John Carey Exhibition (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Life Links (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Mary Ting: Month of Poison (2001), Archival Resource Key; 1 Floppy disc (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Matthew Tischler: Photographic Works (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - A Painter's Legacy - James Gahagan (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Paperworks (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Perspective (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Rest (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Shadows (David Wojnarowicz): Paintings by F. Douglas Blanchard (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Small Works Salon Show (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Small Worlds (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The State of Things (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Susan Hensel: Assembling Memory (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key; 1 Floppy disc (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Uncommon Portrayals (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
  - Weaving Bridges I (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Weaving Bridges II (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - America: Photographs by Jeremi Bialows (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Bon a' tirer: Five Years at Grand Press (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Complexity of Simplicity (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - In the Presence of Family: Photographic Portraits of Brooklyn Families by Ann Rosen (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Matthew Deleget - Archetypes (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - OIA National Juried Exhibition (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16-18)
  - Portraits of Places (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Recent Multiple Projects x 5 (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Recent Works on Paper (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Selections (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Silk Drawings - Akiko Kotani (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Susan Palmisano - Eating Lessons: Recent Paitings (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Transmigrations by Viktor Koen (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Using Double Vision: 7 Representational Painters (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - William Crow - Discursive Spaces (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Brave New World (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28-29)
  - Continuums (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Deluxe (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Faulty Diction: New York by Catherine Gass (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Life Forms and Geometry (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Photography: In Black and White (2003), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Point of Origin (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Shells - Sculpture by Ping-Yu, Pan (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Various Exhibitions, circa 1970s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - Various Exhibitions, circa 1980s-circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Various Exhibitions, circa 1984-circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Various Exhibitions, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Various Exhibitions, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - Various Exhibitions, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Artists' Files, circa 1980-circa 1990s; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.2 Linear feet Box 18
  Artists' files contain various resume materials, slides, and photographs about artists, including Hera, Tom Klem, Mary Shaffer (includes one videocassette), and a few others.
  - Hera, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Klem, Tom, circa 1980-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Shaffer, Mary, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) "A Natural Force" (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Various Artists, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
- Financial and Legal Records, circa 1970s-2002; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 6.9 Linear feet Box 18-25, 29
  Found here are award letters for grants received; grant applications and information; budget materials; check stubs; consultant agreements; deposit books; an event ledger for "Rubin's Roast"; nine exhibition and operations ledgers; fundraising information and funding materials; invoices, bills, and receipts; liability and program insurance materials; receipt books; tax materials and exemptions; Warren Tanner Memorial Fund savings accounts; and legal materials concerning the Richard Serra sculpture debate and the position of the executive director.
  - Audit, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Award Letters, Grants Received, circa 1984-circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Bank Statements, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Budget Information, 1979-circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20-25)
  - Charities Registration, New York State, 1979-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Checks, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Check Stubs, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
  - Consultants, Fee Agreements, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Resolutions Certificate, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Deposit Books, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Deposit Books, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - Deposits, 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5-23)
  - Event Ledger, "Rubin's Roast", 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Financial Reports, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25-28)
  - Financial Reports, circa 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key; 4 Floppy discs (Box 20, Folder 1-24)
  - Funding, circa 1970s-circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 25-28)
  - General Financial Material, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 29-33)
  - General Services Administration, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Grant Materials, circa 1985-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Grant Materials, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
  - Grants, Art Matters, Inc., circa 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Grants, DCA, 1978-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5-12)
  - Grants, Exxon Corporation, circa 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Grants, Marine Midlands Bank, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Grants, Mobile Oil Corporation, 1978-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Grants, Mobile Foundation, Inc., circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Grants, NEA, circa 1980-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17-22)
  - Grants, NYFA, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Grants, NYSCA, circa 1977-circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24-37)
  - Grants, NY Common Grant, circa 1994-circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Grants, Puffin Foundation, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Grants, Rockefeller Brothers, circa 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Grants, SICA, 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Invoices, Bills, and Receipts, 1980-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1-29)
  - Invoices, Bills, and Receipts, circa 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1-26)
  - Invoices, Bills, and Receipts, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1-5)
  - Law and Position of Executive Director, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers, circa 1980s-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7-15)
    Oversized material housed in Box 29, Folder 1.
  - Legal Materials, 1978-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
  - Liability Insurance, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 18-20)
  - OIA Corporation, circa 1977-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Program Insurance, circa 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
  - Receipt Books, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Reimbursements, 1981-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25-27)
  - Richard Serra Sculpture Debate, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
  - Staten Island Fundraising, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Tax Exemption, circa 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Tax Materials, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Tax Materials, 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
  - Warren Tanner Memorial Fund Savings, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
  - Oversized Ledgers, from Box 24, Folder 11, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Printed Material, circa 1970s-circa 2002; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 3.1 Linear feet Boxes 25-29, OV30
  Printed materials include newspaper and magazine clippings, press releases, flyers, OIA newsletters, and reviews. Also included are exhibition announcements and postcards, exhibition catalogs, and posters.
  - Artspeak Newspaper, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, circa 1977-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 9-20)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Press Releases, circa 1970s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 21-25)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Press Releases, circa 1990s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1-15)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1977-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 16-24)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, circa 1990s-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1-8)
  - Exhibition Posters, 1978-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Oversized material housed in Box 29, Folder 2, and OV30.
  - Flyers of Clippings, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Gallery Guides, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - General Exhibition Materials, 1977-circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 12-18)
  - General Printed Material, circa 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Magazines, 1986-circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 20-21)
  - Newsletters, 1977-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 22-24)
  - Newsletters, 1995-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
  - Press Releases, 1977-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - Publicity and Reviews, circa 1970s-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - Oversized Exhibition Posters, from Box 27, Folder 9, 1978-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Oversized Exhibition Posters, from Box 27, Folder 9, 1978-1988; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 30)
- Scrapbooks, circa 1977-2000; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.7 Linear feet Box 28
  Scrapbook titles were devised for clarity.
  Seven dismantled clippings and exhibition scrapbooks contain exhibition materials, slides and photographs, clippings, price lists, and artists' lists, among other materials.
  - Clippings Scrapbook, circa 1977-circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - Exhibition Scrapbook 1, circa 1977-circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - Exhibition Scrapbook 2, circa 1977-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 13-15)
  - Exhibition Scrapbook 3, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition Scrapbook 4, circa 1978-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 17-20)